[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Because you were appointed by President Obama's administration to go and represent the country and a few days later, you came out, what do you make about this whole issue down there of the way they treat homosexuals?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, you know, when I competed at a very young age with Russians, it was illegal for them to be homosexual.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "When you were asked to go and represent your country, by your President to do this, did you have any qualms at all about going there, knowing what the reception is likely to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "VBG", "RB", ",", "VBG", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "If you did, what would you say to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "OITANO: I would probably say it's a privilege to be here as a guest in your country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "IN", "EX", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Is it advisable to do that to provoke the beast if you like so publicly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Well, first of all, I think that the athletes who go over there, they have a task at hand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "Are you worried about the athlete security?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "You know, I think everybody is worried about security but I do think that it's the first priority.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "On a personal level, coming out at 50, I think it was when you did quite recently I mean how did that feel for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "It was difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "How would you describe it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Well, I was pleasantly surprised by the reaction but I wasn't relieved, I wasn't relieved.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "... rather than a great American athlete?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "That's a good point because everybody wants to be known their accomplishments and being gay is one aspect of who I am, you know, I am son, I'm a brother, I'm a cook, I'm everything, I'm an athlete.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 144, "question": "It doesn't get better than that, isn't it Brian?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "It's pretty amazing and it sort of opened my whole demographic up to a lot younger generation.'", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Your new project is called the Boitano Project?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Boitano Project"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Boitano", "Boitano"]}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "POS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "That's kind of a makeover show, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Yeah, it is but I found my great, great grandfather's house in a village where every Boitano came from and I bought it from 20 Boitano's and I renovated it so that I can have my family go there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Why my name is involved and what you have to achieve?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Well, the act itself like you said it would actually just allow people to carry a firearm without a permit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "What's it got to do with me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "... secure that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "And what is your point about the second amendment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "It's a constitutional right that we have that is in shrine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Look, do you know what this is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "What is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "It's Kinder surprise egg.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Would you describe it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, it depends.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Do you know why they're illegal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Because the government has interfered and is trying to protect us from ourselves.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Well, what is the irony?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Well, look, I'm not allowed to eat a chocolate egg in America, it's illegal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 243, "question": "And I can go and buy 2,360 different types of guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "The federal government has become very ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Does that strike you as strange?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "It does indeed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "So you went battleheart (ph) with me to save the Kinder egg for the American people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "I love the Kinder eggs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "What do you think more lives will be saved by flooding the streets with more guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Well, this won't flood the streets with more guns.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "You would -- just to clarify, you want everyone in Oklahoma to have the right to just carry guns, anywhere they wish, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ":", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oklahoma"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "... but therefore, you would like more guns on the streets?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "I think that the more people that carry guns, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Do you really believe that, Senator?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "You really believe that -- presumably of the ultimate, your utopia is that every American wanders around the streets of America armed and that makes it safer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "No, because I'm not going to force anyone to violate what they don't want to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Would you support an assault weapons back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "No, I would not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Would you support universal background checks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "I would not support any of the -- the propositions that they have presented or that you have presented, but you are more than willing to present those solutions as a constitutional amendment just to propose them as a law or as an executive order will not work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "POS", "RB", "VBN", "VBZ", ",", "``", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 304, "question": "What is your argument against knowing whether somebody about to buy gun is mentally insane and can be proven to be mentally insane or is a criminal or has a criminal record, why would you not want to know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "Because the constitution has currently stated that's currently written says, \"The right to keep and bear arms shall not be infringed.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Even if you're mentally insane or criminal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "If you want to amend and change the constitution, there's a way to do that and it's through the amendment process.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "But how do you -- how do you do -- have you been check if they're mentally insane?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "What we need to address the mental health first.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 322, "question": "How do you tackle that if you don't even want to check if they're mentally insane?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Well, if you want to talk about mental health issues, I mean, and if you think that the government is somehow going to protect American citizens against mental health, our government has dropped the ball even on our troops...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "You don't want to have any background checks on guns or whatsoever, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Is your constitutional God-given right to not have any checks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "We are innocent until proven guilty in America.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Well, you're very concerned about mental health being a problem and not the gun, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Mental health is the root of the problem...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "Now, explain to me why that in itself is not completely insane?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "First of all, that's not what I said Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 348, "question": "What is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "... I was saying that...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 350, "question": "What is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "... in regards to mental health...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", ":"], "qSentId": 352, "question": "What is the number one contributor factor of gun violence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "I can answer that one...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Now, if you want I can answer the previous question or this last three that you thrown out at me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "The floor is yours senator.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "AHM: ... in this instance, so what's the next solution?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 372, "question": "What else could it possibly be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Well, like I said, I mean, if you want things to be...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "What is the key contributing factor to gun violence and gun death in America if it's not guns or mental health issues?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "It is a sin nature in mankind.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Yes, how would that be an answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Because then law abiding citizens, good guys would be able protect themselves from bad guys.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Well, I realized that you have also mentioned in your book and then many writings that you want to ban assault weapons in America but not handguns, is that correct?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Well, I think assault weapons are good stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "But you do want to ban handguns as well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "I'm going to find a gun's full stop (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RBR", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "And shotguns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "Well, on this time, more people want guns for hunting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "EX", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Do you agree with him that his son's right to his life should supersede the right of an American to own a military style assault weapon of high capacity magazine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I believe that his son has his right to life and it's very sad news (ph) that there was not somebody there to protect his son.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Is his son's right to life more important than an American's right to own a military style assault weapon and high capacity of magazine as he said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "See, the problem...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Yes or no?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "The problem here Piers is that...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 419, "question": "Would you agree with him or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "You don't understand what rights are, you, yourself said, just a moment ago, that you're fine with people having...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "CC", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Do you agree with him or do you not agree with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "I believe that both of them should and could co-exist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "In other word, you get a Second Amendment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "A well-regulated militia being necessary to the security of a free state.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "POS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "-NONE-", ":"], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Where does the well-regulated militia part come into this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "So, you would say that's it would be fine for militia members and maybe military police to own AK-47...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "What part of that constitutes for the founding fathers in your constitution describes as a well-regulated militia?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Well -- just to clarify again, you are fine with militia members owning AR-15s.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Did you think that most Oklahomans agree with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "I believe so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Who was talking about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Crabtree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "And what kind of adversity do you think he has overcome to get where he has?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Well, you know, it was tough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Talk me through some of those rules and why you think perhaps, at the heart of all these is parental responsibility?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Well, you know, now that I'm a parent, myself, I totally understand everything that our parent put us through, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "But what was your impression when you heard him react like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Well my impression was -- the first thing I said to my brother I said, \"Bro I love you man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Ben, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Good evening Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "I don't think there's ever been such an incredible fast speed domination of the American music chart in history, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "I believe you're right about that, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Let's just say, a cacophony noise, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Well, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "Is this is the same were in Miller?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Yes it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Miller"]}}]